This was right after having
Esto fue justo después de haber
condemned kcu what a coincidence and ahu
condenado kcu qué casualidad y ahu le da
likes the post
like a post
Sprint and also the sentence that you made
Sprint y además la condena que hiciste
was effectively a sentence but it
efectivamente fue una condena pero no
was not the most serious in the world I think that
fue la más grave del mundo creo que
[Music]
[Música]
ual wait what man wait look
ual espérate queo hombre espera Mira
well I thought that it is that what is done
Bueno yo pens
now is that this was
que es que que est hao ahora es que esto
a while ago they can fall like
haido hace un ratino les puede caer como
[ __ ] whatever they want but nimu was
el culo lo que quieran pero a nimu la
traumatized a good girl and they screwed her
traumaron una mina buena y le [__] la
life nimu was a good girl a girl a
vida nimu era una piba bien una pi una
normal girl or at least that's what I knew
piba normal o al menos eso conocía Yo
Then they started to screw the girl they
después a la mina la empezaron a funar
screwed her life and she went out to act
le [__] la vida y salió a hacerse
like she eh I don't know I want to fight with
como la eh No sé me quiero pelear con
everyone I go and get together with Dalas
todo el mundo voy y me junto con Dalas
Anyway it's over nimu they screwed her life
Total ya está a nimu le [__] la vida
nimu I'm cursing you friend Yeah but before
nimu te bardeo amigo Sí pero antes de
barde arme before barde arme
barde arme antes de barde arme pasaron
other things happened do you understand before barde
otras cosas entienden antes de barde
arme nimu was a normal person I
arme nimu era una persona normal me
varied because he had no other choice because he did
varió porque no le quedado otra porque
n't know How to save his
no sabía Cómo salvar su
career nimu please well answer
carrera nimu por favor bueno responde
answer this directly please
responde a esto directamente por favor
friend no  it may be clear I had no choice but
amigo no puede ser claro no me quedaba
to save my career Yeah yeah yeah the
otra para salvar mi carrera Sí sí sí la
[ __ ] of the l dude I already I already I already
concha de la l boludo yo ya yo ya yo ya
said it in private We already had it in a
lo lo dije en privado Ya lo habíamos en
small committee we had talked about it but
petit comité lo habíamos hablado pero
dude the guy doesn't even think it
boludo al chavón no se le pasa por la
's because he did things that
cabeza que es porque hizo cosas que no
weren't good no no because he harassed a
estaban buenas no no porque acosó una
girl No no it's because I had to save
mina No no es porque yo tenía que salvar
my career Sure sure because I had to
mi carrera Claro claro porque tenía que
save my career I started to say what I
salvar mi carrera empecé a decir lo que
had to say but one thing cheer me up
tenía que decir pero una cosa animo
because it is true eh that there was a
porque sí que es verdad eh que hay una
time before delo's podcast So I
época antes del podcast de delo Así que
think it was like in the same Yes in
creo que ha sido como en el mismo Sí en
the same 2023 no that even people from your
el mismo 2023 no que incluso gente de tu
discord leaked to me like you had
discord me filtró como que tú habías
spoken with kcu I don't know if you remember no
hablado con kcu no sé si recuerdas no
kcu Forgive me for saying this about you
kcu Perdóname que he dicho esto de ti
but I mean you were scared it happens that at that
pero o sea tenías miedo pasa que en ese
moment he sent me his explanation his
momento él me mandó su explicación su
version of things he was the first
versión de las cosas fue la primera
person who approached me to tell me
persona que se acercó a mí a decirme las
things eh And he told me ta happened this happened the
cosas eh Y me dijo ta pasó esto pasó el
other eh Fuentes believe me and well I said let's
otro eh Fuentes créeme y bueno yo dije a
see this person never  He didn't do anything bad
ver esta persona nunca me hizo nada malo
to me, in fact, uh, I said it
a mí es más eh yo yo lo dije
openly, he extended a hand to me
abiertamente él me me extendió una mano
at certain times and he never treated me badly at
en ciertos momentos y no me trató mal
all. Eh then I said Okay, I'm
para nada nunca Eh entonces dije Okay le
going to believe him, I mean, I'm going to believe his
voy a creer o sea le voy a creer su
version of the story, which was quite, I do
versión de la historia que era bastante
n't know, it was no, there was no evidence or anything in
No sé era no no había pruebas ni nada en
his version of the story, it was like a
su versión de la historia fue como un
chat and I said, forgive me, there was a version, I
chat y le dije perdoname había versión o
mean, I said, forgive me, this chat is also
sea le dije perdoname este chat igual es
public, uh, because it was read in the podcast
público eh Porque se leyó en el podcast
with Dallas, uh, and I said, Well, sorry, I don't
con Dallas eh Y le dije Bueno Perdón no
know what, but of course because he was the person
sé qué pero claro porque fue la persona
who approached me, he never did anything
que se me acercó él nunca me hizo nada
bad to me, etc., etc., it wasn't out of fear, it
malo etcétera etcétera no fue por miedo
was because, let's see, this person approached me, he
fue por a ver esta persona se acercó me
explained, Okay, I accept it, uh, and until
explicó Okay lo acepto eh Y hasta que no
Dallas showed me the evidence that
fue que Dallas me mostró las pruebas que
I had refused to see, or at least
yo me había negado a ver o al menos no
I wasn't interested. No, it's not like Dallas
me interes No no es como que Dallas
stalked, evidence or whatever, I didn't see it, I didn't see
acosador pruebas o lo que sea no lo vi
anything, I mean, if
no vi nada o sea yo si es que me
something did appear on my Twitter feed, I would
aparecía algo en el feit de Twitter lo
click on it and look at it and the evidence didn't appear,
cliquea y lo miraba y no me aparecieron
heavy that he sent me, you'll
las pruebas heavy que me mandó después
see what it was  it's [ __ ] crazy that we
daras que era una [__] locura que las
saw them with delox not even delox
vimos con delox ni siquiera delox las
had seen them and we were completely crazy
había visto y nos quedamos loquísimos
but what he's holding on to is
pero es que a lo que él se agarra la
his version I do know what
versión de él yo sí la sé a lo que lo
he's holding on to are the nuances that may
que él se agarra es a los matices que a
not be exact Like for example
lo mejor no son exactos Como por ejemplo
no no he doesn't hold on to anything Javi Yes man
no no no se agarra nada Javi Sí hombre
like in minor he says nothing he doesn't say anything he has
como en menor dice nada no dice nada
never responded simply conversa
nunca ha respondido simplemente convers
he didn't say anything no no no he the he didn't
él no dijo nada no no no el la él no
say any version of anything in the
dijo ninguna versión de nada en las
conversations with nimu literally he didn't
conversaciones con nimu literalmente no
say Ah yes you're referring to the
dijo Ah si te refieres a las
conversations the conversations
conversaciones las conversaciones las
we leaked in the podcast itself and they're
filtramos en el en el propio podcast y
all there you saw them in person
están todas ahí las vio dasas en persona
and and he simply says at some point I'm
y y simplemente dice en algún momento le
going to tell him something I don't know I don't know how much and it's
voy a decir algo no sé no sé cuánto y es
believe me source believe me literally but he doesn't
créeme fuente créeme literal pero ni
even say anything in several live shows it's not
siquiera dice nada en varios directos no
the conversations but in several
son las conversaciones sino en varios
live shows he has said that like you're
directos él ha dicho que como que tú
lying and he makes up that she's a minor he
mientes y te inventa que es una menor te
makes up that you drugged her and it's like
inventa que tú la drogaste y es como que
he's holding on to things like eh yes
él se agarra cositas como eh si
dismantling the entire story and the
desmontar el relato entero y la
photograph for example maybe the
fotografía por ejemplo a lo mejor las
chic men  He hasn't said that live,
chic men no lo ha dicho eso en directo
well I would say that he didn't say that. I
bueno diría que eso no lo ha dicho él
think that his defenders told him and the
Creo que se lo dicen sus Defensores y la
and And then why were you
y Y entonces mismo tú por qué estabas
so so just in case there was a
tan tan por si acaso quedaba la
chance that he was right or
probabilidad de que él tuviera razón o
because you had some kind of [ __ ] with
porque tenías algún tipo de mierdo con
the creators there. No no In
los creadores de allí No no De hecho de
fact in fact it is public and it is historical that
hecho es es público y es histórico de
I
que yo con la la comunidad Argentina
have almost no relationship with the Argentine community, I mean no I never
casi tengo ni relación o sea no nunca
had it always been like in some way they
tuve siempre como que de alguna manera
left me quite aside in a lot
me dejaron bastante de lado en un montón
of things, I think the first time they
de cosas creo que la primera vez que me
included me was the Awards Last year they
incluyeron fue los Awards El año pasado
invited me but that was like the
que me invitaron pero eso fue como la
only important interaction I had
única interacción importante que tuve
with the Argentine community So no no
con la comunidad Argentina Así que no no
no nothing to do eh I think that I think that you
no nada que ver eh Creo que creo que
've always had, I mean maybe at that
siempre has tenido o sea igual en ese
time you had like the desire to be
momento tenías como ganas de ser
accepted within certain groups it's you were
aceptada dentro de ciertos grupos es te
afraid of taking it and telling them all to go
daba miedo el [__] y mandarles a todos
to hell it hasn't been until now
a la [__] no ha sido hasta ahora
recently that everyone turned their back on you
recientemente que que todos te dieron de
When they started to denounce you and maybe
lado Cuando te empezaron a funar e igual
now that I remember it there is something else there is something else that I that I that
ahora que lo recuerdo hay otra cosa más
was a great a great striker let's say of
fue un gran un gran percutor digamos de
my  actions as far as being in favor
mis acciones en cuanto a estar a favor
of coscu and and I almost didn't mention this
de coscu y y esto casi ni lo menciono
because I didn't seem to pay attention to it but
porque como que no le daba pelota pero
recently I started thinking about it and I said and I
hace poco me lo puse a pensar y dije e
should have mentioned it because it's
lo tenía que haber mencionado porque es
something important and it's that when when what
algo importante y es que cuando cuando
happened with coscu happened I
yo cuando pasó lo de coscu yo todavía
was still talking to you saw and and I
seguía hablando con que viste y y yo le
passed him the captures I don't know what I don't know
pasaba Las capturas no sé qué no sé
how much and he told me don't go against
cuánto y me decía no te pongas en contra
cosu it's not good for you he told me keno and I
de cosu no te conviene me dijo keno y yo
said oh okay that was one was another of the let's
dije ah okay esa Fue una fue otro de los
say of the most striking of Why did
digamos de los percutores más de Por qué
n't I go against it at the time
no me puse en contra en su momento
because it was like it is more likely if I
porque fue como es más probablemente si
look for the chat on discord I have it but
busco el chat en discord lo tengo pero
what do you think that you because that is clear it is more
qué crees que te porque eso claro es más
than evident Cain herself and those who
que evidente la propia Caín y las que
were with her on the call said it
estaban con ella en llamada lo decían
What can this guy generate for you if you
Qué puede generarte este chico si te
go against it, pu pu he closes you but
pones en contra qu pu pu te cierra pero
not his own, I mean the doors as if you
las suyas no o sea las puertas como si
say that you fight with i i He closes you co he
dices que te peleas con i i Te cierra co
closes the evening and closes you clear
te cierra la velada y te cierra claro
clear is what he told me Clear clear clear
claro es lo que me decí Claro claro
that I couldn't go against  him
claro que yo no me podía poner contra él
because of this whole thing that of course
por todo este tema de que claro se me
a lot of doors were going to close on me,
iban a cerrar un montón de puertas
plus he had invited me to the
además me había invitado hac repco a la
Cos Wars you know and he had nominated me and
Cos Wars viste y me había nominado y
everything and he said No no don't do that
todo y me dijo No no no hagas eso
eh okay I said Okay makes sense
eh okay dije Okay me hace sentido viene
coscu comes and tells me privately I wasn't all
coscu me dice por privado Yo no fui todo
my ex telling me Don't mess with him let's
mi ex diciéndome No te metas con él a
see
ver
eh I mean I explode because on the other hand they
eh o sea exploto porque por otro lado me
are telling me that he is a stalker and I eh I am
están diciendo que es acosador y yo eh
disgusted And I totally condemn those things
repugno Y condeno totalmente esas cosas
so I am like exploding because the
entonces estoy como explotando porque lo
work and the personal get mixed up and on the
laboral y lo personal se mezclan y y por
other hand I don't either I had so much
otro lado yo tampoco Tenía tantas
evidence of cocu so I said Okay what the
pruebas de cocu entonces dije Okay qué
hell am I doing and I came out like a liar
[__] hago y quedé como una mentirosa
my Impartial take is fine and a lot of
mi toma Imparcial queda bien y un montón
other things because and Well of course eh the
de cosas más por y Bueno claro eh al al
human being likes to
ser humano le gusta mucho
generalize a situation and he likes to
generalizar una situación y le gusta
categorize he doesn't like to say he is a
mucho categorizar no le gusta decir es
liar and he is false but they don't know
mentirosa y es falsa pero no saben todo
the whole context behind it they don't know what there is how I
el contexto que hay detrás no saben lo
feel my past
que hay lo como yo me siento mi pasado
this the other who is talking to me who
el esto el otro quién me está hablando
no that what I know what I don't understand I
qui no que lo que sé lo que no ent yo
think that definitely  that might have had an
creo que definitivamente eso pudo haber
effect but I think the underlying reason
hecho efecto pero creo que la razón de
is that Wanting to be
fondo es eso El querer todo el rato ser
accepted within the group all the time that's why you
aceptada dentro del grupo por eso
also
también en las los eventos a los que
told me at the events that you went to Well I don't know if I
llegaste ir me contaste Bueno no sé si
can say this like that about the ghost if you
puedo decir esto cuá ese del fantasma si
can no no no no no no I mean
se puede no no no no no O sea la actitud
your attitude with the streamers and like let's say you did
tuya con los streamers y como tú digamos
n't have a group Ah okay Yes yes yes you
no tenías grupo Ah okay Sí sí sí lo
can say it yes you can say it well
puedes decir s lo puedes decir bueno
nothing I think I've never told this
nada que creo que esto nunca lo conté
same as I've never told this in public
igual esto nunca lo conté en público
but come on here's another exclusive for Javi he
pero venga va otra exclusiva para Javi
already has another excerpt he smiles and Lu
ya tiene otro extracto sonríe y Lu se
complains that we're throwing members away I'm going to
queja de que regamos miembros yo voy a
sleep tonight like it happened eh I told you that to
dormir hoy como dio eh yo te dije que a
give December late I don't know if you
dar diciembre atrasado no sé si
prefer what you want me to say my
prefieres de lo t quieres que diga yo mi
opinion is a it's a it's a it's a
opinión es un es que es un es que es un
pattern and it's good it's good it's
patrón y está bueno está bueno está
good to clarify well that I have been
bueno clarificar bueno que yo a lo que
able to know a little more about you eh I
he podido saber un poco más de ti eh
think that you are a person
creo que eres una persona
who requires the validation of the group or
que requiere la validación del grupo o
at least required it at that moment
al menos lo requería en ese momento
before you realized that everyone
antes de darte cuenta de que todos te
left you aside and that you went all the
dejaron de lado y que tú fueras todo el
time to the  events alone and that you tried to
rato a los eventos sola y que intentaras
uh hang out with people all the time that's why you
eh juntarte todo el rato con la gente
had so many pictures with everyone and you
por eso tenías tantas fotos con todos y
posted so many pictures with everyone
colgabas tantas fotos con todos
definitely feeling the need to
definitivamente sentir laa necesidad de
go with the crowd and what
ir con la masa y lo que iba a la masa lo
the crowd did was either support or
que hacía la masa era o bien apoyar o
whitewash or not say anything
bien blanquear o bien no decir nada
about the abuser of coscu So
sobre el abusador de coscu Entonces
I think that's where
pienso que ahí es donde radica
probably the most relevant part
probablemente la la parte más relevante
of all your need for validation lies, to
de de todo tu necesidad de de validación
be accepted let's say in a group that
de ser aceptada digamos en un grupo que
later you realized that they didn't
luego te diste cuenta de que no te no te
want you at all because the thing about them
querían para nada porque lo de que te
telling you soft block you have to
diron soft block eso tienes que
explain that well you already put it on
explicarlo bueno ya lo pusiste en
Twitter but explain it here too we've
Twitter pero explícalo por aquí también
been talking about that no that I think that I think I
hemos estado hablando de eso no eso creo
mentioned it yeah Well
que que creo que lo mencioné sí Bueno
but I'll mention it again in case you didn't
pero lo vuelvo a mencionar por si no lo
hear that a couple of days after
escucharon que un par de días después de
having condemned kcu soft blocked me
haber condenado kcu me sof bloqueó
Sprint type it was like from Instagram
Sprint tipo fue como desde de Instagram
and Twitter it's very strong that uh it's that
y de Twitter es muy fuerte eso eh es que
yes because also des after the first
sí porque además des después el primero
to come and say and tell me Oh that this that
en venir y decir y decirme Ah que esto
the shipping that you did this that you
que el shipeo que hiciste esto que
did the  another me with him I never messed around
hiciste el otro yo con él jamás me metí
and he comes and does that to me of course What a
onda y viene y me hace eso claro Qué
coincidence that it was just right after
casualidad que justo fue justo después
having convicted coscu what a coincidence
de haber condenado coscu qué casualidad
and now cku likes a Sprint post
y ahora cku le da like a post de Sprint
eh eh attacking me So it's like it
eh eh atacándome Entonces es como me
makes all the sense in the world to me now and
hace todo el sentido del mundo ahora y
also the sentence that you gave
además la condena que hiciste
was effectively a sentence but it
efectivamente fue una condena pero no
was not the most serious in the world I mean you could have been
fue la más grave del mundo o sea podrías
like much stronger it
haber sido como mucho más fuerte no
couldn't have been stronger and the worst thing
podría haber sido más fuerte y lo peor
is that it was saying crazy first [ __ ] he
es que fue decir loco primero cabrón le
told him He called him abuser He said ccu He is an
dijo Le dijo abusador Le dijo ccu Es un
abuser and an abuser of I mean what do you
abusador y abusador de O sea que que
want them to call 91 no no no I mean it
quiere que llaman 91 no no no me refiero
wasn't like with malice you know I mean he
que no fue como con saña sabes o sea
said things objectively but it
dijo las cosas de forma objetiva pero
could have been much much much more
podría haber sido mucho mucho mucho más
aggressive you know and no And you know what the worst thing was
agresiva sabes y no Y sabes qué lo peor
my sentence was honest
que fueron fue fue honesta mi condena
really because I in the podcast eh
realmente porque yo en el podcast eh
When you told me condemn convicted
Cuando vos me decías condeno condenado
I said It's that I can't do it I don't have
Yo decía Es que no puedo hacerlo no me
the moral to condemn someone if I do
da la moral de condenar a alguien si es
n't know what they did right or I didn't see the
que no sé lo que hizo bien o no vi las
evidence or whatever so that's why
pruebas o lo que sea entonces por eso
we made a deal  in which I was going to
quedamos en un trato en el que yo iba a
see the evidence and if he really believed that
ver las pruebas y si realmente creía que
the guy was an abuser or whatever he
el chavón era abusador o lo que fuera lo
was going to say it and if not, no, because at that
iba a decir y si no no porque no ya ese
point I had nothing to lose, not to
punto no tenía nada que perder no
specify what I just said. It's not that
concretar lo que acabo de decir No es
no, no, you didn't condemn him because you
que no no la no le condenaras porque sí
did, what I'm saying is that what I'm saying is that it
que lo hiciste lo que digo es que lo que
could be strong for me is that he
digo es que podría para mí fuerte es que
would have dedicated himself to insulting him on
se hubiese dedicado a insultarle por
top of that or criticizing him more on
encima de eso o a criticar más por
top of that. The only thing he said was the
encima de Eso lo único que dijo fue la
objective phrase that what he did was
frase objetiva de que lo que hizo fue un
abuse, you know. I mean, no, it didn't go any further. It's
abuso sabes O sea no no fue más allá Es
my point that it wasn't more, he didn't go any
es mi punto que no fue más no se ensañó
further and even though he didn't go any further, eh,
más y a pesar de que no se ensañó más eh
these people, the Sprint clown and all
esta gentuza el Sprint payasin y toda
these scum blocked, blocked,
esta Escoria le hizo bloqueo bloqueo
unblocked him. But the thing is that I think
desbloqueo Pero es que yo creo que no
we're not realizing how serious it is, it's
nos estamos dando cuenta de lo grave es
very serious, because look, Spring, I still think he
muy grave pues mira todavía Spring creo
has some kind of relationship with
que tiene algún tipo de relación con
Koku, just like he has with the
koku al igual que la tiene con el
Demented one, for example, but Ari Gameplays and
Demente por ejemplo pero Ari Gameplays y
Juan guarnizo that after
Juan guarnizo que después de la defensa
Ari's defense, Juan came out to assure that Ari didn't  I
de Ari salió Juan a asegurar que Ari no
knew Ari He also came out to assure
lo sabía Ari También salió a asegurar
that you don't remember I mean what does
que no lo os acordáis O sea qué tiene
Ari have to do with coku for me to do
que ver Ari con coku para que le haga
softlock animu because with a I mean I
softlock animu porque con a o sea yo eso
can do that to him he gets involved or
se lo puedo hacer se mete o acusa en
falsely accuses a friend of mine of something but
falso a un amigo mío de algo pero
imagine if I do it to him
imagínate que yo se lo hago
because you mess with gref well what do I have to
porque te metas con gref sea que tengo
do with him it's the group it's the
que ver yo con él es el grupo es el
group it's the the movement of the group
grupo es el el el movimiento del grupo
the movement of the group is what defines
el movimiento del grupo es lo que define
the actions of the group and if the group
las acciones del grupo y si el grupo no
does nothing the rest keep quiet and you know what the
hace nada el resto se callan y sabes lo
hell we had the other
que concón que habamos llevado el otro
day Chatting there with dasas is that those
día Charlando ahí con dasas es que los
who go in a group are always the ones who
que van en grupo siempre son los que
win because they go socially accepted we are
ganan porque van socialmente aceptad los
left alone and like we can't get to
quedamos solitos y tipo no conseguimos
a group we are the
llegar a un grupo somos las el saco de
punching bag of the internet that's how it is and and it's
boxeo de internet así es y y es
screwed it's screwed because it ends up
rejodidos es rejodidos porque termina
monopolizing the opinions and ends up let's
monopolizando las opiniones y termina a
see now spr comes and attacks me for free
ver ahora viene spr me ataca de gratis
without me having said anything to him and now
sin que yo le haya dicho nada y ahora
Hello Papo I don't know what And he with all let's
Hola Papo no sé qué Y él con toda
say the influence he
digamos la influencia que tiene
obviously has eh that I  Today
obviamente eh que me perjudica la Hoy me
my older brother spoke to me that re Boomer he does
habló mi hermano mayor que re Boomer él
n't look at networks he's the typical peasant who does
no Mira redes es el típico campesino que
n't look at networks and he came to ask me what
no Mira redes y me vino a preguntar
happened imagine the impact it
había pasado imagínate el impacto que
has and he told me that Sprint I don't know what I
tiene y me dijo que Sprint no sé qué O
mean imagine the impact it has that
sea imagínate el impacto que tiene que
my peasant brother who has no
mi hermano campesino que no tiene ni
idea about networks comes to talk to me on
idea de redes me venga a hablar a
WhatsApp to ask me what happened or so
WhatsApp a preguntarme qué pasó o sea
you Knowing you Sprint
entonces vos Sabiendo vos Sprint
knowing that you have so much influence you
sabiendo que tenés tanta influencia me
come to attack me for free knowing that I
venís a atacar de gratis sabiendo que yo
never did anything to you I never had anything
nunca te hice nada nunca tuve nada en
against you and I even get along and
contra de vos y hasta te llevar bien y
you made those blogs about coscu I
me hiciste esos blog por lo de coscu o
mean I don't know how I don't know how you have the nerve
sea no sé có no sé cómo te da la cara
friend it disgusted me a lot when he
amigo a mí me dio mucho asco cuando te
answered you that's why I answered because it was
respondió por eso respondí yo porque fue
like I mean for him to come to you and say
como O sea que que te venga a ti a decir
that you hang out with people for
que tú te juntas con gente por
convenience which may be if in the
conveniencia que puede ser si en el
past you have done it that you have hung out
pasado lo has hecho que te has juntado
with people for convenience but what's happening
con gente por conveniencia pero lo de
now is not convenience Rather I
ahora no es conveniencia Más bien yo lo
consider it in some way as anger and
considero de alguna manera como rabia y
at the same time realizing how
al mismo tiempo darte cuenta de cómo son
things are eh but for
las cosas eh pero que eso lo venga
a person to come and say that  literally
diciendo una persona que literalmente
collaborates with an abuser, I mean, how can he
colabora con un abusador o sea cómo va a
have the nerve to talk about
tener la cara tan dura de hablar de con
who you hang out with when he hangs out with and
quién te juntas tú cuando él se junta y
defends a [ __ ] abuser, it
defiende a un puñetero abusador es que
's incredible, just like that, and he's
es increíble tal cual tal cual cu y está
in the same group of people,
en el mismo grupo de la gente esta que
well, from what I understood,
bueno es que yo según tenía entendido
Juan and spr call each other badly or was it a meme or more, I have no
Juan y spr se llan mal o era meme n más
idea, no idea, what
ni idea ni idea lo que está claro a ver
is clear is that there is an
lo que está claro es que hay una hay una
elite, a group, whatever you want to call it, no, I do
élite un grupo como queráis llamarlo no
n't think they're like an
no creo que sean como una élite
organized elite there that handles everything,
organizada ahí que van manejando todo
but it is clear that it is
pero sí que está claro que está está
seen as good to talk about certain people,
bien visto hablar de ciertas personas
good, and seen as bad, eh, to talk well about other
bien y mal visto eh hablar bien de otras
people, if you speak well of Dallas you are
personas si hablas bien de Dallas eres
a bad person, it's wrong because Dallas
una mala persona está mal porque Dallas
is bad, and on the contrary, if you speak uh
Es malo y Y de lo contrario Si hablas eh
badly of Dallas, it is seen as good, it is what it
mal de Dallas está bien visto es lo que
is, that's what is popular. So at the end
está así es lo popular Entonces al final
of the day there are two groups in the elite, and
del día hay dos grupos en la élite yd Y
this is something that everyone knows, it's
esto es algo que todo el mundo sabe es
an open secret, there are the people who
un Secreto a voces está la gente que
are on the side of Dallas and the people who are not,
está al lado de Dallas y la gente que no
I think it's ridiculous. This goes beyond the
me parece ridículo Esto va más allá del
Dallas issue, and that, I  I, I think, I think that what
tema Dallas Y eso yo yo yo creo yo creo
happens there is that
que ahí lo que pasa es que a raíz de eso
kcu comes from that because obviously it is clear
viene kcu porque obviamente está claro
that coscu and Dallas there is a rivalry that is not
que coscu y Dallas hay una rivalidad no
visible to everyone and these
a la vista de todo el mundo está y esta
people when they have to choose whether to support
gente cuando tiene que elegir si apoyar
or harm people who are
o perjudicar a gente que está
harming people in their group in the end it
perjudicando gente de su grupo al final
is a herd effect it is a hive effect they mess
es efecto manada es efecto Colmena se
with coscu attacked this one they mess
meten con coscu ataco a esta se meten
with I don't know who attacked example to me wiu
con no s quién atac ejemplo a mí wiu me
seems like one of the worst people on the
parece de las peores personas que hay en
internet but I would not defend someone
internet pero yo no defendería a alguien
like koku because he was on
como koku porque estuviera del lado de
Wi michu's side Well but for some reason we are on
Wi michu Bueno pero por algo estamos en
this call and not on a call with Ari
esta llamada y no en una llamada con Ari
Gameplays like because we have
Gameplays en plan porque tenemos sentido
common sense or I mean let me explain it is that
común o sea me explico es que es así de
easy those people those people the problem The
fácil esa gente esa gente el problema El
problem of course they are defending a
problema claro están defendiendo un
very strong fact they are not defending Oh
hecho muy fuerte no están defendiendo Ay
but it is that Dallas makes me very bad because they do not care
pero es que Dallas me qu muy mal porque
but you have seen have you
les da igual pero tú has visto tú has
seen that those people have had the
visto que esa gente han tenido los
balls to tell nimus we are your
[__] de decirle a nimus somos tus
friends we are going to go to Disney and then three
amigos vamos a ir a Disney y luego tres
Doritos after free give him a
Doritos después de gratis meterle un
ratio of 8 million interactions
ratio de 8 millones de interacciones
Simply because well I also have to
Simplemente porque bueno Igual igual te
correct you there because the one who
tengo que corregir ahí porque o sea el
gave me the ratio was Sprint and Sprint
que me tiró el ratio fue Sprint y Sprint
wasn't on that call but he did it
no estaba en esa llamada pero lo hizo
because he was responding to Juan I
porque le estaba respondiendo a a a Juan
mean it was irrelevant No no no it was
es decir no venía al caso de nada No no
irrelevant I totally
no que no venía al caso Totalmente de
agree it was irrelevant I understand I mean nimu
acuerdo no venía al
was
caso Yo entiendo O sea nimu estaba
responding to Juan guarnizo and
respondiéndole a Juan guarnizo y
then
entonces
uh Sprint responded to that tweet from nimu
eh Sprint respondió ese tweet de nimu
talking about Juan that Juan was
hablando sobre Juan que Juan estaba
attacking nimu the thing is that nimu
atacando a nimu la cosa es que nimu
basically is the simple punching bag
básicamente es el saco de boxeos
right now uh And then you know
sencillo ahora mismo eh Y entonces saben
anything you say to her
que cualquier cosa que le digan a ella
literally uh the guy would respond to
literalmente eh el tipo respondía a
anything and automatically get
cualquier cosa y automáticamente tenía
more likes than her but it's the same as
más likes que ella pero es que es igual
with me I mean I also have a
que conmigo o sea yo también tengo una
similar situation Obviously with their
situación parecida Obviamente con sus
differences but look this idiot
diferencias pero fíjate que el tonto
responded to me c ass fart pee
este me respondía c culo pedo pis
literally that and he had more likes than
literalmente eso y tenía más likes que
me so it matters it matters if the
yo entonces importa importa siqua los
likes don't what it only shows
likes no lo que único que demuestra que
is that there are people dumber than smart in
es que hay gente más tonta que lista en
this world and that's it I always thought
este mundo y ya está yo siempre Pensaba
like that and the thing is it doesn't give a [ __ ]
así y y la cuestión es importa una [__]
[ __ ] I don't  it doesn't matter the likes I
[__] no me importa nada los likes O
mean there are times when you're right and you get
sea hay veces que tienes razón y tienes
more likes But there are times when you're not
más likes Pero hay veces que no tienes
right or you literally say nothing
razón o que literalmente no dices nada
you say poop ass fart pee and you get more
dices caca culo pedo pis y tienes más
likes just because Well because you have a
likes solo por qué Pues porque tienes un
bunch of 9 year old girls who are
montón de niñas de 9 años que te se
dedicated to following you and have ID to beat you like you
dedican a seguirte y ha ID latarte como
were a caper which I will
si fueras un capoper cosa que no tendré
never have because the guy really is
nunca jamás porque el tipo de verdad es
an illiterate Careful But anyway the
un analfabeto de Cuidado Pero bueno la
thing is yes tell me what were you going to say no no that I was
cosa es que sí dime qué ibas a decir no
just going to put that
no que que justo iba a meter que
Talking Talking about people who for
Hablando Hablando de gente que que por
saying stupid things get more likes than the
decir estupideces gana más likes que la
person who is right So to speak
persona que tiene razón Por así decirlo
eh Jasmine is drinking dude I
eh la Jasmín esta la beber boludo me la
saw it coming eh I wanted to say it
veía venir eh tenía una ganas de decirlo
dude there was a girl she couldn't
boludo que había una mina no se podía
contain herself eh but no I don't know it I don't
contener eh pero no no me la sé no me la
know it I
sé Esa
offered to do a debate with the two of them I
les ofrecí hacer un debate a las dos yo
put a post on Twitter I don't remember what the
puse un post en Twitter no recuerdo qué
[ __ ] it was but some stupid thing you said the
[__] era pero una tontería dijiste la
elite is going to fall some stupid thing Oh yeah I put it it's
élite va a caer una tontería Ah sí puse
going to fall on you and it's coming this one
la el te va a caer y viene est esta
Random and she tells me yes nimu that you funas
Random y me dice que sí nimu que t funas
don't make you important I don't know what and and I do
no te hacen importante no sé qué y y yo
n't know what I answered her she tells me and
no sé qué le respondí ella me dice y
she always with more you answered her that
ella siempre con más le respondiste que
even if you're sexualizing because she
siquiera siqua como sexualizando porque
has a bat Oh sure because I entered
tiene una bat Ah claro porque yo entré a
her Stream that was just live The
su Stream que justo estaba en vivo La
girl and she's moaning with ASMR did you see
piba y la está gimiendo con asmr viste
the typical ASMR microphone that you get close
el típico micrófono asmr que te acercas
and you moan into the microphone she's doing the
y gemis en el micrófono está haciendo el
Stream like if you donated gim to me or
Stream así como si me donaste gim o
things like that and I and I entered the Stream and I
cosas así y yo y yo entré al Stream y le
started laughing and I made the comment I
me caé risa y le puse el comentario le
said Well yes yes I kept moaning
dije Bueno sí sí seguí gimiendo en
live that we're not going to buy fans to which she
directo que no vamos a comprar to fans a
already answers me a little Simi 30,000 I don't
lo que ya me contesta a poco Simi 30.000
know what I don't know how much and she has more
no sé qué no sé cuánto y ella tiene más
likes than me with the 30,000 that we
likes que yo con lo de 30.000 que
just saw in this very live
acabamos de ver en este mismísimo
that is worthless because no I
directo que no vale para nada porque no
'm not involved in that So of course
no estoy implicada en eso Entonces clar
if you had my video you even see it it's that it
si tenías mi video incluso lo ves es que
's ridiculous because people and the
es que es ridículo porque la gente y la
mine have more likes and  people saying
mina tiene más likes y la gente diciendo
Uh the rep I eat nimu of course with lies
Uh la rep papeo animu claro con mentiras
anyone eats with with defamation
cualquiera papea con con difamaciones
anyone eats I can say tomorrow
cualquiera papea yo puedo decir mañana
that she is a pedophile and I eat her but
que ella es pedófila y la papeo pero
of course it is a lie So it is the
claro es una mentira Entonces es la
injustice no well let's see what
injusticia no bueno a ver qué que
you put here I love these
pusiste acá Me encantan estos titulares
personal headlines it is which one is which one
sonales es cuál es el que Cuál es el que
is on Dallas's side at the
está del lado de Dallas en estos
moment it is understood that nmu no let's see and
momentos se entiende que nmu no a ver y
neither because it is Yes well Of course because
tampoco porque es Sí bueno Claro porque
Dallas has messed with Sprint then
Dallas se ha metido con Sprint entonces
Sprint is the [ __ ] boss I mean I
Sprint es el [__] amo o sea yo me
get up in the morning and I say What is the
levanto por la mañana y digo Cuál es la
controversy today Sprint has eaten nimu
polémica de hoy Sprint ha papeado a nimu
or nimu has eaten Sprint what side has
o nimu ha papeado a Sprint a de qué lado
Dallas taken against Sprint
se ha puesto Dallas en contra de Sprint
nimu with tears and Sprint base it is it
nimu con lágrimas y Sprint basadisimo es
literally eh is that literally dude No
es literal eh es eso literalmente tío No
but seeing you know seeing that cover on the
pero ver sabes que ver esa portada en el
tur plant Channel makes me feel that
Canal de tur plant me hace sentir que
I am that I am that I am on the
estoy que estoy que estoy en lado
right side dude Because if Turbo
correcto boludo Porque si Turbo me
defended me he would say uh uh what happened Uy
defendiera diría uh uh lo que pas Uy
screwed that  guy who takes steps and falls
cagu ese chavón que do pasos y se cae
on himself
encima
dude Hey let's see what we see the
boludo Oye vemos lo de vemos las
words that windy dedicated to you
palabras que os ha dedicado windy
after the podcast and we'll go now if you
después del podcast y nos vamos ya si os
think so no Come on I'm a little in shock
parece no Dale estoy un poco en chock
because the podcast that I recorded itself fear
porque el podcast que grabé en si miedo
of success is having a very good
al éxito está teniendo muy buena
reception almost 99% of the
receptividad casi el 99% de los
comments are practically positive
comentarios prácticamente son positivos
and they are supporting me a lot imo and I want to
y me están apoyando much imo y quiero
thank you very much if you haven't seen the
agradecérselo mucho si no has visto el
podcast I'll put it here I recommend
podcast te lo pongo aquí te recomiendo
that you watch it it's very good and very
que lo veas está muy bueno y muy
revealing I want to thank simeo for the
revelador Quiero agradecer a simeo el
success delox and nimu for having me as a
éxito a delox y a nimu por tenerme
guest and for giving me a worthy place
invitada y por darme un lugar digno
where my voice could be heard and I
donde mi voz pudo ser escuchada y en
'm really in shock I'm loving
verdad estoy en shock me está encantando
this
este
2024 I'm leaving the podcast here for you to
2024 les dejo el podcast aquí para que
watch and I love you all 2024 is the
lo vean y los quiero mucho el 2024 es la
best
[__]
Hey good night
Eh Buenas noches
[Music]
[Música]
pap is going to come he's going to give a hard time now
pap va a venir va meter una bronca ahora
you told me three hours ago that he was going to
de tú me dijiste hace TR horas que iba a
come man that we hooked up
venir hombre que nos hemos enrollado yo
now I'm going to
ahora voy
record a video for but I don't know how
grabar un vide para pero que no se la
difficult it is  gust
difícil que le gust
being people I hadn't realized I'm
estando personas no me había dado cuenta
going to tell you not to play hard to get
te voy a decir que no se haga el difícil
that he left and came back I invited him
que se fue y volvió a entrar Lo invit
Because he starts watching it you know what the
Porque se pone a verlo sabes cuál es lo
only thing is that of course as if we didn't count on
único que claro como como no contábamos
this it was unprepared because I
con esto ha sido sin preparar pues me he
left the spectators the events The
dejado los espectadores los eventos El
PayPal the encore a all the things on the
PayPal el bis un todas las cosas por
screen and cover a little there but oh well
pantalla y tapa un poco ahí pero bueno
what a shame that he left the PayPal
qué lástima que haya dejado el PayPal
on the screen and cover eh What a shame
por pantalla y tape eh Qué lástima
because he wanted to take this one to upload
porque este lo quería [__] para subir
his video I'm going to have the editor that does a
su vídeo I va a tener el editor que da
somersault But oh well eh For that Cobra
voltereta Pero bueno eh Para eso Cobra
that nothing guys Hey eh a pleasure let's see
que nada chicos Oye eh un placer a ver
if Come more often no couple what do you
si Vení más a menudo no parejita qué te
like eh You like to force interaction
gusta eh Te gusta forzar la interacción
eh Javi whoever does the chipeo like this let's see
eh Javi el que haga el chipeo así a ver
if we become with him creoa and and we
si nos convertimos con el creoa y y nos
go viral I haven't said anything the
ponemos viral yo no he dicho nada el
chipeo I said couple let's see if two
chipeo yo he dicho parejita a ver si dos
friends you don't know who I've spoken to today Who I've
amigos no sabes con quién he hablado hoy
spoken to Cry with today don't
Con quiénes con Cry he hablado hoy no
[ __ ] with you stop there at least you didn't
jodas para í para ahí al poca no te la
want to keep it son of a thousand what have I  said that I've
quisiste guardar hijo de mil qué lo he
spoken to him I haven't said
dicho que he hablado con él no he dicho
anything else I said that I've spoken to him
nada más he dicho que he hablado con él
since you take out the c I tell you that I've
ya que sacas el c yo te digo que he
spoken to c because it ended well with
hablado con c porque ha acabado bien con
windy I thanked him but let's
windy le dado las gracias pero deja
spoil it
spoilear
left Okay guys good night We say
dejao Bueno chicos buenas noches Nos
goodbye But you thank him
despedimos Pero tú le das las gracias
because it ended well with windy you are
porque ha acabado bien con windy t eres
a SIM like the r it's not because I had
un SIM como el r no es porque Antes
left before it's because I had
había dejado es porque Antes había
left a message before inviting him to the
dejado un mensajito invitándole al
podcast and since he didn't respond I
podcast y como no me respondió le he
put in another interaction and I invited him again
metido otra interacción y le he vuelto a
and nothing and what he told me we're not
invitar y nada y lo que me ha dicho no
going to reveal So nothing friends
lo vamos a desvelar Así que nada amigos
good night we have
buenas noches
realized Hey eh guys No
nos hemos dado cuenta Oye eh chicos No
seriously Thank you so much for having
en serio Muchísimas gracias por haber
spent the night here with me the truth is
echado aquí la noche conmigo la verdad
that I had a great time and I think
que me lo he pasado muy bien y creo que
the people did too and that here is
la gente también y que aquí tenéis
your home thank you very much Javi
vuestra casa dale muchas gracias Javi
that's how I get into the podcast about all your
así me elito podcast lo de todas sus
social networks they told me they told me every
redes sociales me decían me decían cada
time you talk they told me every time you
vez que hablas me decían cada vez que
talk spam as and I say don't [ __ ] with me I'm going
hablas spame as y digo no te jodes le vo
to give Javis exclusives here and I'm
a dar aquí exclusivas a javis y yo te
going to you  to spam as much as I can
voy a meter spam hasta donde no pueda
apart This is delox's gossip channel,
aparte Este es el canal de salseo de
that is, he has his little channel
delox o sea él tiene su canal de poca
But then he comes here to talk and he
Pero luego él viene aquí a hablar y
also said it I don't know if it was in the other one
además lo dijo No sé si fue en el otro
that made me thank you very much I think it was
que me hizo muchas gracias creo que fue
in the podcast not with windy says no I'm just
en el podcast no con windy dice no Yo es
that when I'm going to give my opinion I have to go to
que cuando voy a opinar tengo me voy a
another channel and As I think I told you I
otro canal y Como creo que te lo dije
think I told you when I came for the
Creo que te lo dije a ti cuando vine por
rewan hispano is that I don't have
lo del rewan hispano es que yo no tengo
time to do so many channels
tiempo para para hacer tantos canales
So I prefer to come here talk
Entonces yo prefiero venir aquí hablar
about gossip I don't care about giving you the
del salseo me da igual darte las
exclusives because I've been in the chavera for
exclusivas porque yo soy de la chavería
I know two TR years before I
desde hace yo sé dos TR años antes de de
had the podcast and all that
que tuviera el podcast y todo eso
So for me I see myself very
Entonces para mí yo me veo muy
represented with the chat I am one more
representado con el chat yo soy uno más
of the chat but now Well, I have a
del chat pero que ahora Bueno pues tengo
voice Well, just like n just like nimu nimu
voz Pues igual que n igual que nimu nimu
is from the chavalera I know for three or cu years
es de la chavalería se ya tres o cu años
well maybe when you put it in when
bueno quizá cuando le metiste cuando le
you put the 10 videos Maybe not the first
metiste los 10 vídeos Quiz no el primer
sub you can see the expression with the
sub se le nota la expresión con el
doll a kiss a kiss very handsome muchim
muñeco un beso un beso guapísimo muchim
a kiss a
un beso un
I kiss goodnight to
beso buenas noches a
[Music]
[Música]
everyone
todos